<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2017 Nicholas van Dyke
  ~
  ~ This file is subject to the terms and conditions defined in 'LICENSE.md'
  -->

<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">

    <string name="app_name">Sia Mobile</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">close</string>
    <string name="unlock_wallet">Unlock wallet</string>
    <string name="lock_wallet">Lock wallet</string>
    <string name="create_wallet">Create wallet</string>
    <string name="view_addresses">View addresses</string>
    <string name="view_seeds">View seeds</string>
    <string name="sweep_seed">Sweep seed</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change password</string>
    <string name="hosting">Hosting</string>
    <string name="wallet">Wallet</string>
    <string name="terminal">Terminal</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="seed">Seed</string>
    <string name="sweep">Sweep</string>
    <string name="seed_warning">Keep your seed(s) safe! You will need them to recover your funds if something happens to your device or wallet. If someone gets your seed(s), they can take your funds!</string>
    <string name="recipient_address">Recipient address</string>
    <string name="amount_sc">Amount (SC)</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="receive">Receive</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="not_synced">Not synced</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="unlock">Unlock</string>
    <string name="current_password">Current password</string>
    <string name="new_password">New password</string>
    <string name="confirm_new_password">Confirm new password</string>
    <string name="change">Change</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>

    <string name="terminal_warning" tools:ignore="TypographyDashes">ADVANCED:\nThis terminal uses siac as its backend. Siac is a command-line utility written by the
        Sia developers that can interface with all of Sia\'s API endpoints; you can type --help and press enter for a list
        of commands. The purpose of this terminal and its use of siac is to make available to you commands that might not
        yet be part of the mobile graphical interface. While siac is fully functional on a computer, very little testing of
        it has been done on a mobile device. Functionality is not guaranteed. Use at your own risk.\n\nIf you\'re running a local full node,
        it\'s output will also appear here.\n\n</string>

    <!--Strings for explaining install-->
    <string name="step_5" formatted="false" tools:ignore="TypographyDashes"><![CDATA[5. In the same command prompt, type\n\nsiad --disable-api-security --authenticate-api
    --api-addr <ip>:<port>\n\nreplacing <ip> with your computer\'s internal IP address from step 4, and <port> with a port number
    of your choosing; remember your port number for later. This step will launch Sia on your computer in a fashion that
    allows Sia Mobile to interact with it. You will need to keep this command prompt open and running to use Sia Mobile with it. If you instead downloaded Sia-UI in step 1, also add\n\n
-d %APPDATA%\\Sia-UI\\sia\\\n\nto the command above, as this is the directory that Sia-UI stores its files in by default.]]></string>

    <string name="step_8"><![CDATA[8. (optional) Following the steps above, you will only be able to access your
computer\'s Sia from your phone when your phone is on the same network as your computer. In order to access it from anywhere, you will have to port forward on your
router on your chosen port to your computer\'s internal IP address. Many guides exist online detailing how to do this. Please note that the Sia API uses HTTP requests,
which are NOT inherently secure. If you communicate with your full node from outside your local network, other people can potentially see the info you are sending
and receiving. This is not a concern if you will not be port forwarding your node.]]></string>
    <string name="synced">Synced</string>
    <string name="syncing">Syncing</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="renter">Renter</string>

</resources>
